So I was going to talk about the young man who was murdered in the subway by a white man who was allowed to walk away because black lives do not matter in this country.
I was going to talk about the tragedy of life that was lost today in yet another mass shooting in Atlanta.
And there was just a myriad of other terrible things that have happened today that I feel always compelled to talk about, but I don't want to talk about it.
So I'm just going to ask you to donate to Smart, Funny, and Black.
We are given the opportunity to provide 140 tickets to folks who cannot afford to come to the show.
And so for those of you all who want to support Smart, Funny, and Black, but don't live in LA, you can go to smartfunnyandblack.com.
You can donate however much you want to give.
And that donation will go to providing tickets to the individuals who cannot attend the show because inflation be inflationing.
I literally created Smart, Funny, and Black because we need a place to celebrate because we are seeing so much black tragedy on a daily freaking basis
that we have to have somewhere to revitalize.
May 18th in LA, Smart, Funny, and Black at the Novo.
Wayne Brady versus Jaleel White.
See you there.